https://www.sitescapesonline.com/terms-of-use.asp

Custom
More...
Wynne
More...
Acceptance of Terms
Please read the SiteScapes Terms of Use carefully before you accept these Terms by: (a) submitting contact information to SiteScapesOnline, and/or (b) using SiteScapesOnline website in any other manner. If You do not agree to all of these terms, do not use this Website. The Terms are entered into by and between
SiteScapes and You. If you are using the Services
on behalf of your employer, you represent that you are authorized to accept these Terms on your employer's behalf. SiteScapes provides on-line resources accessible via SiteScapesOnline.com to You, subject to the Terms. Unless explicitly stated otherwise, the Terms will govern your use of any new features that augment or enhance the current Services, including the release of new SiteScapes resources.
Obligations
In consideration of Your use of the Services, You agree to be solely responsible for: (a) providing true, accurate, current, and complete information as prompted by the registration form and (b) maintaining and promptly updating the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. You are solely responsible for the security of your password. You acknowledge and agree that certain Services may provide password-restricted access to customer information such as product drawings, quoting, and ordering. By using this Website and registering for such Services, you consent to SiteScapes's Terms of Use and accept all risks of unauthorized access to such information. If You provide any information that is false, inaccurate, out of date, or incomplete, or SiteScapes has reasonable grounds to suspect that such information is false, inaccurate, not current, or incomplete, SiteScapes may suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the Services.
Confidentiality of Information
In order to gain access to the Services, You agree to these confidentiality provisions: You acknowledge that you may obtain direct
access via the Website to certain SiteScape
confidential information. You agree, either as an individual or on behalf of your employer, to be bound by the provisions of this Section. Furthermore, if you are acting on behalf of Your employer, your employer agrees to indemnify You for violations of this Section.
SiteScapes,Inc. hereby grants you, only upon your acceptance of these terms and conditions, only the following non-exclusive rights to use the posted Drawings:
a. You may use the Drawings, in electronic or hard copy formats, for incorporation into your architecture project drawings or your architecture plan estimates where your project drawings or your plan estimates are then used to bid on or design architecture jobs for your clients, potential clients or other designers, provided that you reproduce all copyright notices and other proprietary notices on each copy made.
b. You may not use the Drawings for a purpose that relates to you or another making the object(s) depicted in the Drawings or a purpose which in any way uses the Drawings to create another similar, related or complimentary object(s).
You must not remove, overprint, or deface any notice of copyright, trademark, logo, legend, or other notice of ownership from any documents from the Services.
EXCEPT AS STATED ABOVE, YOU MAY NOT COPY, TRANSFER, DISTRIBUTE, OR DISCLOSE DRAWINGS TO OTHERS, AND ANY UNAUTHORIZED COPYING, TRANSFER, DISTRIBUTION, DISCLOSURE, OR USE SHALL AUTOMATICALLY TERMINATE YOUR LICENSE.
Proprietary Rights and Copyrights
The Drawings and the information contained therein are the exclusive, confidential and proprietary property of SiteScapes Inc.. The Drawings are copyrighted with all rights reserved. Under confidential and proprietary property laws and the copyright laws, each Drawing may not be copied, in whole or in part, without written consent from SiteScapes except as provided herein. The same confidential, proprietary and copyright notices must be affixed to any permitted copies as were affixed to the original. Any unauthorized use of any Content contained on this Website may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes.
Notices, Modification
and Termination of Services
SiteScapes reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Services (or any part thereof) with or without notice. SiteScapes, in its sole discretion, may terminate Your password, My SiteScapes account, use of the Services or use of any other SiteScapes service, and remove and discard any Content within the Services, for any reason, including, without limitation, for lack of use or if SiteScapes believes that You have violated or acted inconsistently with the letter or spirit of the Terms. Any termination of Your access to the Services under any provision of the Terms may be effected without prior notice, and SiteScapes may immediately de-activate or delete Your My SiteScapes account and all related information and files in Your My SiteScapes account and/or bar any further access to such files or the Services. Further, SiteScapes will not be liable to You or any third-party for any termination, modification, or suspension of the Services.
Member Account, Password and Security
If any of the Services requires you to open an account, you must complete the registration process by providing us with current, complete and accurate information as prompted by the applicable registration form. You also will choose a password and a user name. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to notify SiteScapes immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. SiteScapes will not be liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your password or account, either with or without your knowledge. However, you could be held liable for losses incurred by SiteScapes or another party due to someone else using your account or password. You may not use anyone else's account at any time, without the permission of the account holder.
Links
This Website may be linked to other websites which are not under the control of and are not maintained by SiteScapes. SiteScapes is not responsible for the content of those sites. SiteScapes is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply endorsement by SiteScapes of those sites.
Privacy Policy
SiteScapes respects Your desire for privacy. SiteScapes' Privacy Policy can be found here. By using the Website, You are consenting to the processing of Your data by SiteScapes and consenting to the terms of our Privacy Policy. Should SiteScapes decide to make changes to its privacy policy you will be informed and given an option to have your information removed from SiteScape systems.
General Information
This Website could include inaccuracies or typographical errors. SiteScapes and the Third Party Providers may make improvements and/or changes in the products, services, programs, and prices described in this Website at any time without notice. Changes are periodically made to the Website. SiteScapes may amend these Terms at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. These Terms represent the entire understanding relating to the use of the Website and prevail over any prior or contemporaneous, conflicting, or additional, communications.
Copyright Notice
Copyright © 2002-6 SiteScapes Inc., P.O. Box 22326, Lincoln, Nebraska 68542 U.S.A. All rights reserved.
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
More...
More...
© 2015 SiteScapes Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Sale
Terms of Use
SiteMap
